Mohammed Adel

Back-End software engineer

Contacts:

<u>Tel:</u> +201004677123

Email: adl774855@gmail.com

Github: https://github.com/M-0x4D

<u>Linked in :</u> https://www.linkedin.com/in/m-0x4d/

Summery:

This is Mohamed Adel works as a Back-End developer with +2 years experience as PHP Laravel developer and graduated at 2022 and exempted from the army. I created many systems at study period using many technologies but I finally settled on Laravel technology from two years ago.

EXPERIENCE:

Back-end developer at Tecsee internetagentur [Oct 2022 - present]

- -> works on jtl-shop german framework in php to create ecommerce apps and we customed plugins in this framework and it allow to us to make this custom plugins.
- -Back-End Developer trainee

Ipda3 Tech | AUG 2022 - Oct 2022

-> learnt PHP Laravel Framework and applying on 2 projects (BloodBank, Sofra).

Education:

[Sep 2017 –July 2022]

Mansoura College Academy | Bachelor's Degree - Electronics and Communications Engineering .

Skills:

Laravel - php - MySql - Git&Github - Html - Css - bootstrab - javascript - jquery - Ajax - rest Api -Server knowledge [AWS – Azure] - docker – problem solving – oop .

Projects:

Php & Laravel projects:

→ Payment System [Web – Api]:

- This is electronic payment method or gateway which could be used in websites to use it in paying like ecommerce systems and others.
- ⇒ Used services : [multi auth spatie validation api mail seeders mysql]
- ⇒ Link : Payment-System

→ Fundding System [Web – Api]:

- This is donations system which people can use it to donate to charities or hospitals or other organizations, this system uses my own payment gateway for funding or payment.
- ⇒ Used services : [multi auth spatie validation api mail seeders mysql eloquent dashboard]
- ⇒ Link : Funding-System

→ Blood bank System [Web – Api]:

- This is blood bank system which used to help people to donate with them blood and can post medical posts to share medical knowledge with others.
- □ Used services : [multi auth spatie validation api mail seeders mysql eloquent dashboard custom validation]
- ⇒ Link : Blood-Bank

→ E-commerce System [Web – Api]:

- This is e-commerce system for buing and selling products in many catigories , I used also my own payment system in this app too to pay money.
- Used services: [multi auth spatie validation api mail seeders mysql eloquent - dashboard - custom validation]
- ⇒ Link : E-commerce-System

→ Supervisors & Employees management System [Web – Api] :

- Supervisors have a big problem to handle projects and tasks with the employees and this system helps them to do that .
- Used services: [multi auth spatie validation api mail seeders mysql]
- ⇒ Link : Supervisore&Employees management system

→ Booking website in php native :

- This site used to book appointments or dates for doctors or other one need to book an appointment and it use txt files to save data in it and used also txt files to authenticate users and I saved my routes for authenticated users only
- Used services : [php native txt files for storing data html css javascript]
- Link: booking website

Other projects:

→ Honeypot System [Graduation project] :

- This system consists of two server :
 - -> The first one is vulnerable server consists of vulnerable web service in php which vulnerable to [+] command injection [+] XXE and binary service in c which vulnerable to stack based buffer over flow .
 - => Link : <u>Honeypot Server</u>
 - -> The second one is MHN server to collect data about the attacker consists of web service in Django framework.

=> Links : MHN-Server - MHN-Mobile-App

- → Screen recorder software :
 - ⇒ Link: https://github.com/M-0x4D/screen recoreder
- → Screen recorder malware :
 - ⇒ Link: https://github.com/M-0x4D/ScreenRecord malware
- → Webcam malware:
 - ⇒ Link: https://github.com/M-0x4D/webcam malware
- → Reverse shell malware :
 - ⇒ Link: https://github.com/M-0x4D/ReverseShell malware
- → Ransomware :
 - ⇒ Link: https://github.com/M-0x4D/ransomware
- → Key logger :
 - ⇒ Link: https://github.com/M-0x4D/keylogger malware
- → Back door :
 - ⇒ Link: https://github.com/M-0x4D/BackDoor malware